http://smtinspection.com/pages/privacy

Shopping Cart
Your cart is currently empty.
My Account
Welcome to SMTinspection.com!
Privacy Policy
SMTinspection.com and its parent company WA Brown Industrial Sales are fully committed to maintaining the highest level of privacy for our customers, vendors and employees. At no time will any of your personal or corporate information be shared with any of our suppliers, vendors or business partners except where needed to process your orders with us.
I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at this site. The following discloses how I gather and disseminate information for this website.
RSS Feeds and Email Updates
If a user wishes to subscribe to my RSS Feeds or Email Updates (powered by Feedburner), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users may opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party. (You will never be spammed by me - ever)
Log Files and Stats
Like most websites I use log files, in this case Statcounter or Google Analytics. This stores information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring, exit and visited pages, platform used, date/time stamp, track user’s movement in the whole, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This website may use cookies. However, some of my business partners use cookies on this site (for example - advertisers). I can't access or control these cookies once the advertisers have set them.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. I suggest my users to be aware of this when they leave this site and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Advertisers
I may use outside ad companies to display ads on this blog. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the advertising companies and I do not have access to this information. I work with the following advertising companies: Google Adsense, Amazon affiliates, Clickbank and others. Please check the advertisers websites for respective privacy policies.
This privacy policy updated August 2015
Call Toll Free 877-962-6847
Save 5% on Your Next order!
Get special pricing, free shipping and more...
Sign up for Savings
Subscribe
© 2020 SMTinspection.com
